homeemploymentagency.net 2010-12-29

# Privacy « Home Employment Agency

**Collection of your Personal Information**

www.homeemploymentagency.net collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Profit System Online also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by homeemploymentagency.net. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by homeemploymentagency.net for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of homeemploymentagency.net Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through homeemploymentagency.net public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: homeemploymentagency.net does not read any of your private online communications.

homeemploymentagency.net encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from homeemploymentagency.net so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. homeemploymentagency.net is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of homeemploymentagency.net and homeemploymentagency.net family of Web sites. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

homeemploymentagency.net collects and uses your personal information to operate homeemploymentagency.net Web site and deliver the services you have requested. homeemploymentagency.net also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from homeemploymentagency.net and its affiliates. homeemploymentagency.net may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

homeemploymentagency.net does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. homeemploymentagency.net may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, homeemploymentagency.net may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to homeemploymentagency.net, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

homeemploymentagency.net does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

homeemploymentagency.net keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within homeemploymentagency.net, in order to determine what homeemploymentagency.net services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within homeemploymentagency.net to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

homeemploymentagency.net Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on homeemploymentagency.net or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of homeemploymentagency.net; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of homeemploymentagency.net, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

homeemploymentagency.net Web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize homeemploymentagency.net pages, or register with homeemploymentagency.net site or services, a cookie helps homeemploymentagency.net to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same homeemploymentagency.net Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use homeemploymentagency.net features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of homeemploymentagency.net services or Web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

homeemploymentagency.net secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. homeemploymentagency.net secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

By viewing this Web site, you agree that you have waived any and all claims of any kind or nature that could be brought against this website concerning the loss, alteration or misuse of information. You must be aware that it is possible for your personal data to potentially be obtained by unauthorized users, such as “hackers” and used in an inappropriate manner that may result in harm to you. In the event that your personal information is subject to unauthorized access, you acknowledge and agree that homeemploymentagency.net is not responsible for the actions of the unauthorized users, and you waive your right to file any claims or causes of action against homeemploymentagency.net arising out of the unauthorized use of your personal information.

**Changes to this Statement**

homeemploymentagency.net will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. homeemploymentagency.net encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how homeemploymentagency.net is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

homeemploymentagency.net welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that homeemploymentagency.net has not adhered to this Statement, please contact homeemploymentagency.net at Email. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.  
Discretion to Use Information. THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATIONFOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY’S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how the Company currently uses Individual Information, but the Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, the Company may update this policy from time to time. The Company may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, SMS text messaging, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.  
SMS Wireless Policy  
We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider’s standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS  
correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending “STOP”, “END”, “QUIT” replying to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.  
(a) Detailed Wireless Policy (addendum) Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider’s name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider’s standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.  
We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.  
You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to support@homeemploymentagency.net or by sending “STOP”, “END”, “QUIT” to the SMS text message you have received.

***INCOME CLAIM WARNING:** Testimonials are not typical of most results. Photographs or images are a depiction of individuals and payment methods. These income examples are representative of some of the most successful participants in the program. Some individuals purchasing the program may make little or NO MONEY AT ALL. These claims are not a guarantee of your income, nor are they typical of average participants. Individual results will vary greatly and in accordance to your input, determination, hard work, and ability to follow directions. No person or company can guarantee profits or freedom from loss. Any and all use of this website certifies you are agreeing to our Earnings and Income Disclaimers.

*For purposes of privacy, the creator of Home Employment Agency is using the name Elizabeth Jackson. This story is based upon the real life adaptation of the parties involved. The Company reserves the rights to the name and any uses of it as affiliated with the product. Any improper uses by unauthorized parties is strictly prohibited. 

***TESTIMONIALS** \- All Testimonials are 100% Real and Accurate and the attestants have been remunerated for allowing Home Employment Agency's use of the same. For the sake of customer privacy, Home Employment Agency reserves the right to protect and/or substitute the images of attestants. The images displayed hereon are not the actual images of the attestants. The images displayed hereon have been supplied by Home Employment Agency and are the copyrighted property of Home Employment Agency. 

****AFFILIATION/BRANDS** \- Home Employment Agency is not affiliated with, endorsed by or in any way associated with Apple, Coleman, Adidas, Compaq, The New York Times, Esquire, America Online, CNN, USA Today, Forbes, Yahoo. Home Employment Agency does not have the express permission of Apple, Coleman, Adidas, Compaq, The New York Times, Esquire, America Online, CNN, USA Today, Forbes, or Yahoo logo. 

**NOTICE** \- Anyone found copying Home Employment Agency's website or using Home Employment Agency's trademarked/copyrighted text and/or images without Home Employment Agency's express written consent will be reported to their billing company, their hosting company, and any other related companies or necessary parties for account closure. Home Employment Agency will also follow with a copyright infringement lawsuit in accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). 

The entire contents of this website are Copyright © 2010 http://www.homeemploymentagency.net. All rights reserved. This site may not be copied in whole or in part without the express written permission of the publisher. All violators will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.
